export default data = [
    {
        question: "Mangoes are a _____ fruit here in Taiwan; most of them reach their peak of sweetness in July",
        options: ["mature","usual","seasonal","particular"],
        correct_option: "seasonal"
    },
    {
        question: "Writing term papers and giving oral reports are typical course _____ for college students",
        options: ["requirements","techniques","situations","principles"],
        correct_option: "requirements"
    },
    {
        question: "If we work hard to _____ our dreams when we are young, we will not feel that we missed out on something when we get old",
        options: ["distribute","fulfill","convince","monitor"],
        correct_option: "fulfill"
    },
    {
        question: "Few people will trust you if you continue making _____ promises and never make efforts to keep them",
        options: ["chilly","liberal","hollow","definite"],
        correct_option: "hollow"
    },
    {
        question: "Becky _____ her ankle while she was playing tennis last week. Now it still hurts badly",
        options: ["slipped","dumped","twisted","recovered"],
        correct_option: "twisted"
    },
    {
        question: "Research shows that men and women usually think differently. For example, they have quite different _____ about what marriage means in their life",
        options: ["decisions","beliefs","styles","degrees"],
        correct_option: "beliefs"
    },
    {
        question: "The new manager is very _____. For instance, the employees are given much shorter deadlines for the same tasks than before",
        options: ["persuasive","tolerable","suspicious","demanding"],
        correct_option: "demanding"
    },
    {
        question: "While the couple were looking _____ for their missing children, the kids were actually having fun in the woods nearby",
        options: ["anxiously","precisely","evidently","distinctly"],
        correct_option: "anxiously"
    },
    {
        question: "After delivering a very powerful speech, the award winner was _____ by a group of fans asking for her signature",
        options: ["deposited","reserved","vanished","surrounded"],
        correct_option: "surrounded"
    },
    {
        question: "The interviewees were trying very hard to _____ the interviewers that they were very capable and should be given the job",
        options: ["credit","impress","relieve","acquire"],
        correct_option: "impress"
    },
    {
        question: "After the first snow of the year, the entire grassland disappeared under a _____ of snow",
        options: ["flake","blossom","blanket","flash"],
        correct_option: "blanket"
    },
    {
        question: "Peter likes books with wide _____, which provide him with enough space to write notes",
        options: ["angles","margins","exceptions","limitations"],
        correct_option: "margins"
    },
    {
        question: "At the beginning of the semester, the teacher told the students that late assignments would receive a low grade as a _____",
        options: ["hardship","comment","bargain","penalty"],
        correct_option: "penalty"
    },
    {
        question: "Various studies have been _____ in this hospital to explore the link between a high-fat diet and cancer",
        options: ["conducted","confirmed","implied","improved"],
        correct_option: "conducted"
    },
    {
        question: "Intense, fast-moving fires raged across much of California last week. The _____ firestorm has claimed the lives of thirty people",
        options: ["efficient","reliable","massive","adequate"],
        correct_option: "massive"
    },
  ]
  